Guide to the Alfred E. Kahn papers, 1942-1994
Kahn, Alfred E. papers, 1942-1994
- Series XVIII. Videos
  - The Advocates-Election '80 (WGBH-TV) Interview; Boston, MA, Sep. 23, 1980; V-7150 (Box 140)
  - Inflation Briefing with Mr. Schultze (Tape III), V-7151 (Box 140)
  - The Inflation File (Reel 1 of 1 / Tape VIII); San Diego, CA, V-7152 (Box 140)
  - Inflation Briefing with Mr. Kahn (Tape I); Washington, D.C., Dec. 19, 1978; V-7153 (Box 140)
  - Inflation Briefing and Q and A with Mr. Caddell (Tape II); Washington, D.C., V-7154 (Box 140)